alexpad.com 2014-03-21

# Privacy policy

This privacy policy is valid personal information with respect to any information from users of the service alexpad.com (the service) and is subject to strict execution only in compliance customer service operation rules. Operation service is unconditional consent of the user with this privacy policy. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy, the user must refrain from usage of the service. Service administration reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy. 

**Providing maintenance services administration service alexpad.com seriously approaches the question of confidentiality and trust of customers, respects and protects the integrity of your personal information and make every effort your personal information maintained in the strictest confidence. We do not provide information about your data to third parties and endeavor to ensure their integrity and confidentiality. An exception may be the personal information request which carried some payment systems, such service transmits requests directly to the user, such information is usually removed at the end of service payment transaction.**

In this Policy under "Personal Information Users" means: 

  * Personal information that the user provides about himself alone in the registration process (creating an account) when. 
  * Data exchanged service during its operation with the help of the machine's user software. 
  * Other information required for the service within the services provided to them. 

This Policy applies only to service alexpad.com. Administration Service does not control and is not responsible for third party sites to which the user can go to the links generated and (or) available from service, through its operation. On these sites, users can collect or ask for other personal information, and can also perform other actions. Service does not check the validity of personal information provided by users, and does not control her. Consequences of providing false information by the user, as well as other fraud identified **User Agreement** and **operating rules** service.
